const quizQuestionsArray = [
  {
    question: 'Who is the main character in SpongeBob SquarePants?',
    option1: 'Patrick Star',
    option2: 'Squidward Tentacles',
    option3: 'Sandy Cheeks',
    option4: 'SpongeBob SquarePants',
    answer: 'SpongeBob SquarePants'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the animated movie featuring a rat who aspires to be a chef?',
    option1: 'Finding Nemo',
    option2: 'Toy Story',
    option3: 'Ratatouille',
    option4: 'Up',
    answer: 'Ratatouille'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which cartoon character lives in a pineapple under the sea?',
    option1: 'Scooby-Doo',
    option2: 'Tom and Jerry',
    option3: 'Bugs Bunny',
    option4: 'SpongeBob SquarePants',
    answer: 'SpongeBob SquarePants'
  },
  {
    question: 'In "Tom and Jerry," what type of animal is Tom?',
    option1: 'Mouse',
    option2: 'Cat',
    option3: 'Dog',
    option4: 'Bird',
    answer: 'Cat'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the family in "The Simpsons"?',
    option1: 'The Johnsons',
    option2: 'The Smiths',
    option3: 'The Simpsons',
    option4: 'The Parkers',
    answer: 'The Simpsons'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which cartoon features a boy and his robot dog exploring the post-apocalyptic world?',
    option1: 'Adventure Time',
    option2: 'Regular Show',
    option3: 'Rick and Morty',
    option4: 'The Amazing World of Gumball',
    answer: 'Adventure Time'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the blue, fast hedgehog in video games and cartoons?',
    option1: 'Mario',
    option2: 'Sonic',
    option3: 'Crash',
    option4: 'Spyro',
    answer: 'Sonic'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which Disney princess has a chameleon sidekick named Pascal?',
    option1: 'Cinderella',
    option2: 'Ariel',
    option3: 'Rapunzel',
    option4: 'Belle',
    answer: 'Rapunzel'
  },
  {
    question: 'In "Pokémon," what is the name of the main character who wants to become a Pokémon Master?',
    option1: 'Ash Ketchum',
    option2: 'Gary Oak',
    option3: 'Brock',
    option4: 'Misty',
    answer: 'Ash Ketchum'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is the antagonist in "The Lion King"?',
    option1: 'Simba',
    option2: 'Mufasa',
    option3: 'Scar',
    option4: 'Timon',
    answer: 'Scar'
  }
];

export { quizQuestionsArray }
